https://www.moonstone-jewelry.com/privacy-policy.html?osCsid=othgj0c7d35lk02n54edrjueg0

QUICK SEARCH
Any GemstoneNo GemstoneAlexandrite (lab)AmethystAquamarineBlack Star SapphireBlue Star SapphireChrome DiopsideCitrineCubic ZirconiaDiamondDino BoneEmeraldFresh Water PearlGarnetIoliteJadeLabradoriteLapisMalachiteMoonstoneOnyxOpalPeach MoonstonePearlPeridotPink TourmalineRhodolite GarnetRubyRuby Star SapphireSapphireTopazTourmalineTsavorite (lab)Turquoise
Any MaterialSilverGoldMixed MetalTitanium
Any StylePendants & PinsRingsEarringsBraceletsChains
Any PriceUp to $50$50-$99$100-$249$250-$499$500-$999$1000 and above
Privacy Policy
Rest assured Moonstone Jewelry takes your privacy very seriously. Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy. Our policy is based on the principles of notice, choice, access and security in the collection and use of all information regarding our users and their activities at our site. Please review this policy each time you use the site as it is subject to change without notice. Note: This policy tells you, among other things, what information we gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information and our efforts to protect it. Please read this policy carefully and feel free to contact us if you have any questions regarding its content.
Types of Information Collected
When orders are placed, we collect billing and shipping information. We also collect the information you disclose when you sign up for our newsletter. We only collect personal information from customers in order to process billing, fulfill orders and provide a personal and customized shopping experience. We use your personal information to identify you as a user of the site and to assist and speed the completion of transactions on the site. We may use your email address to contact you directly regarding services or products that we believe may be of interest to you. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers will only receive telephone contact from us concerning purchases or direct inquiries made by such persons. We may also associate your personally identifying information with information we collect about your preferences and activities at the site, such as the particular pages you request at the site and purchases or other transactions you effect through the site. We may vary the content you receive in future visits to the site based on your preferences and activities.We provide to certain third-party service providers such personally identifiable or other information as is necessary for those third-party service providers to perform services for us, including credit card processing, shipping, database management, Internet services, and marketing or survey services. We require such third party service providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with our privacy practices. All of our third-party service providers must confirm their policy to never use customer's personal information for marketing or promotional purposes. If the personal information that has been gathered from you changes or you no longer desire our service, we will gladly correct, update or remove any personal data you have provided. To request a change or removal of your personal information, use our Contact Us form to send us a message or contact one of our customer service associates at 1-800-557-4583
Third-Party Web BeaconsWe use third-party web beacons from Google Analytics to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Google may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. All information is anonymous, and no personal information is ever used for this process.Updates to Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy supersedes and replaces all of our previous privacy policies. From time to time, we may update this privacy policy. Notice of any such updates which contain any material changes will be posted on our Website. You are encouraged to check our Website periodically for any material changes to this privacy policy.contact us
HOME | ABOUT US | SHIPPING OPTIONS | VIEW
CART | CONTACT USCustom Design | Guarantee & Policies | Privacy Policy
Gold & Silver Prices | Gemstone FactsCopyright © 2020 Moonstone Jewelry Co.
